<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-03-06T16:01:53+00:00</updated><id>//feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Sound Of Thunder</title><subtitle>A PVP and PVE alliance in EVE Online
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">On Intelligence In War</title><link href="//blog/2023/tsoth-intelligence-database/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Intelligence In War" /><published>2023-03-01T15:59:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-01T15:59:00+00:00</updated><id>//blog/2023/tsoth-intelligence-database</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2023/tsoth-intelligence-database/"><![CDATA[<p>Sun Tzu famously said that if you know the enemy, you need not fear the result of 100 battles. Over the past few months, TSOTH have been applying his teachings to our war against Pandemic Horde in EVE with the launch of our intelligence database which is already paying dividends. Before ganking a player, we always run their name through the system, pulling up a list of any chats logs where they were active in the last 48 hours. We check for tags like “bait”, which is a note we add to the files of any player known to fly bait fittings, and then make an educated guess as to whether the risks are justified.</p>

<p>Our horde spy alts upload to the database all the chat logs of every horde channel they are in. There has been a few cases where a Horde player was foolish enough to discuss moving their capital ship in a channel they thought was secure. Routine searches of our database, with the search parameters to show every chatlog in the last 2 hours where a player has used the phrase “moving my archon” or similar, has allowed us to pass intel onto other groups in a timely manner, and arrange for that capital to be destroyed during its move</p>

<p>Of course there has been a few teething problems with the system as well. Carlos Warren briefly crashed the system when he tried uploading a lot of chatlogs all at once (over 15,000 individual files) briefly overwhelming the system. Since then we only upload one day of chatlogs at a time. Also, when Horde found out that we get push notifications when certain keywords are mentioned in their Discord, a few wise asses decided to try and spam the system by saying “carlos” over and over again. This required us to add a filter system, where you can disable keyword notifications from certain players. This is an ongoing process of learning, and adapting. TSOTH acknowledges how important accurate and timely intelligence is, especially when fighting an alliance much larger than us.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="intelligence" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why TSOTH Is And Will Always Be Two Steps Ahead]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Possible Peace Treaty With Pandemic Horde</title><link href="//blog/2022/peace-treaty-with-pandemic-horde/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Possible Peace Treaty With Pandemic Horde" /><published>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</updated><id>//blog/2022/peace-treaty-with-pandemic-horde</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2022/peace-treaty-with-pandemic-horde/"><![CDATA[<p>At one point the mere thought of it would be as incomprehensible as BoB and Goons forming a truce, or Valve releasing HL3 on time. TSOTH and Horde have been locked in a bitter conflict for years, but now some are beginning to speculate that a peace deal might be worked out between the two rival powers. What the exact terms of such a treaty would be is as yet unclear, but we can make a number of educated guesses.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Horde is likely to insist on a complete cessation of all aggression and cloaky camping of their ratters and miners by TSOTH forces</li>
  <li>They may also seek reimbursement for infrastructure that TSOTH destroyed while evicting them from Kalevala</li>
  <li>TSOTH will likely want unimpeded access to certain Horde systems for mining. It is no secret that TSOTH want to expand their mining and industrial base but have been severely hampered by their lack of access to null ores.  It is thought this is one of their main motivations for coming to the negotiating table.</li>
  <li>Both powers may want access to each others structures in space</li>
  <li>Carlos Warren apparently wants Horde to remove the blanket ban on any TSOTH member joining Horde. While he accepts he personally is unlikely to be taken off it (and has no intentions of joining even if he was) he acknowledges that the initial war with Horde started because of a merc contract he accepted that took us into battle with them. He considers it unfair that other corp members, who may wish to leave TSOTH at some stage, be penalized for his actions.</li>
</ul>

<p>It remains to be seen whether any kind of peace deal can be hashed out. There is years of arguments and mutual distrust between the two powers that diplomats on both sides will have to contend with if they want to see a successful deal established. Stay tuned to find out more.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="pvp" /><category term="warfare" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could Two Arch Rivals Be On The Brink Of Peace?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TSOTH Declares War Against The Blue Donut</title><link href="//blog/2022/tsoth-launches-attack-against-nuilsec/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TSOTH Declares War Against The Blue Donut" /><published>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</updated><id>//blog/2022/tsoth-launches-attack-against-nuilsec</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2022/tsoth-launches-attack-against-nuilsec/"><![CDATA[<p>The Sound Of Thunder has started military operations against all the major nullsec powers in EVE, launching simultaneous wardecs against Pandemic Horde and Goonswarm Federation. For months there had been rumours of a planned winter offensive but CEO Carlos Warren had always refused to comment. With todays announcement, he has finally revealed more detail</p>

<p><i>“This campaign has been in the planning stages for a long time. Myself and the other TSOTH directors feel that now is the time for TSOTH to aggressively strike at the existing power structures of nullsec. Our corporation is known for its strong views on this issue. TSOTH’s vision for nullsec is that it should be lots of little independent groups all battling it out, rather than a stagnant world of superpowers and blue donuts. So today we are launching this attack against the two current main superpowers (Panfam and Goons) with the aim of inflicting severe damage to their power base. I will be honest, and admit I don’t think we can completely dismantle these powerblocs alone. Obviously we will try but it may not be achievable. However, we think that once people start to hear of our efforts, when word spreads that a small independent group has stood up to the blue donut and said enough is enough, it will inspire other groups to rise up and do the same.</i></p>

<p>We have launched a <a href="/warupdates">Live War Updates</a> page which you can use to keep track of any developments</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="pvp" /><category term="warfare" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major military offensive underway by TSOTH forces]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog" /><published>2022-04-24T00:20:09+01:00</published><updated>2022-04-24T00:20:09+01:00</updated><id>//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>