<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-01-20T15:34:46+00:00</updated><id>//feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Sound Of Thunder</title><subtitle>A PVP and PVE alliance in EVE Online
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Possible Peace Treaty With Pandemic Horde</title><link href="//blog/2022/peace-treaty-with-pandemic-horde/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Possible Peace Treaty With Pandemic Horde" /><published>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</updated><id>//blog/2022/peace-treaty-with-pandemic-horde</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2022/peace-treaty-with-pandemic-horde/"><![CDATA[<p><img style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" src="https://tsoth.neocities.org/images/peacedeal.png" width="583" height="311" /></p>

<p>At one point the mere thought of it would be as incomprehensible as BoB and Goons forming a truce, or Valve releasing HL3 on time. TSOTH and Horde have been locked in a bitter conflict for years, but now some are beginning to speculate that a peace deal might be worked out between the two rival powers. What the exact terms of such a treaty would be is as yet unclear, but we can make a number of educated guesses.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Horde is likely to insist on a complete cessation of all aggression and cloaky camping of their ratters and miners by TSOTH forces</li>
  <li>They may also seek reimbursement for infrastructure that TSOTH destroyed while evicting them from Kalevala</li>
  <li>TSOTH will likely want unimpeded access to certain Horde systems for mining. It is no secret that TSOTH want to expand their mining and industrial base but have been severely hampered by their lack of access to null ores.  It is thought this is one of their main motivations for coming to the negotiating table.</li>
  <li>Both powers may want access to each others structures in space</li>
  <li>Carlos Warren apparently wants Horde to remove the blanket ban on any TSOTH member joining Horde. While he accepts he personally is unlikely to be taken off it (and has no intentions of joining even if he was) he acknowledges that the initial war with Horde started because of a merc contract he accepted that took us into battle with them. He considers it unfair that other corp members, who may wish to leave TSOTH at some stage, be penalized for his actions.</li>
</ul>

<p>It remains to be seen whether any kind of peace deal can be hashed out. There is years of arguments and mutual distrust between the two powers that diplomats on both sides will have to contend with if they want to see a successful deal established. Stay tuned to find out more.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="pvp" /><category term="warfare" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could Two Arch Rivals Be On The Brink Of Peace?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TSOTH Declares War Against The Blue Donut</title><link href="//blog/2022/tsoth-launches-attack-against-nuilsec/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TSOTH Declares War Against The Blue Donut" /><published>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-10-10T16:59:00+01:00</updated><id>//blog/2022/tsoth-launches-attack-against-nuilsec</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2022/tsoth-launches-attack-against-nuilsec/"><![CDATA[<p>The Sound Of Thunder has started military operations against all the major nullsec powers in EVE, launching simultaneous wardecs against Pandemic Horde and Goonswarm Federation. For months there had been rumours of a planned winter offensive but CEO Carlos Warren had always refused to comment. With todays announcement, he has finally revealed more detail</p>

<p><i>“This campaign has been in the planning stages for a long time. Myself and the other TSOTH directors feel that now is the time for TSOTH to aggressively strike at the existing power structures of nullsec. Our corporation is known for its strong views on this issue. TSOTH’s vision for nullsec is that it should be lots of little independent groups all battling it out, rather than a stagnant world of superpowers and blue donuts. So today we are launching this attack against the two current main superpowers (Panfam and Goons) with the aim of inflicting severe damage to their power base. I will be honest, and admit I don’t think we can completely dismantle these powerblocs alone. Obviously we will try but it may not be achievable. However, we think that once people start to hear of our efforts, when word spreads that a small independent group has stood up to the blue donut and said enough is enough, it will inspire other groups to rise up and do the same.</i></p>

<p>We have launched a <a href="https://tsoth.neocities.org/warupdates.html">Live War Updates</a> page which you can use to keep track of any developments</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="pvp" /><category term="warfare" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major military offensive underway by TSOTH forces]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog" /><published>2022-04-24T00:20:09+01:00</published><updated>2022-04-24T00:20:09+01:00</updated><id>//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>